question_data = [
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The flag of South Africa features 7 colours.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},

    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The Kingdom of Prussia briefly held land in Estonia.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},

    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Former United States Presidents John Adams and Thomas Jefferson died within hours of each other.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},

    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the game &quot;Subnautica&quot;, a &quot;Spadefish&quot; will attack you.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},

    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Scatman John&#039;s real name was John Paul Larkin.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},

    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "&quot;Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater&quot; was released in 2004.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},

    {"category": "Entertainment: Board Games", "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "&quot;Rich Uncle Pennybags&quot; from the board game &quot;Monopoly&quot; wears a monocle.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},

    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "An episode of &quot;The Simpsons&quot; is dedicated to Moe Szyslak&#039;s bar rag.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},

    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "A scalene triangle has two sides of equal length.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},

    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Vietnam&#039;s national flag is a red star in front of a yellow background.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
